Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/jacobjeffrey (LinkedIn)

Jeff Jacob

Archview

Greater New York City Area

Summary

Co-founder and managing member of Archview Investment Group. Prior to co-founding the Investment Manager, Mr. Jacob was a founding member and head of Citigroup's Global Special Situations Group (GSSG) in North America, Latin America, and Europe from 2004 to 2008. Prior to co-founding GSSG at Citi, Mr. Jacob was head of Citigroup's Distressed Debt and Bankruptcy Claim Trading group from 1999 to 2004. At Citigroup, Mr. Jacob served on the Fixed Income, Currency and Commodity Management Committee and the Fixed Income Diversity Committee. Prior to joining Citigroup, Mr. Jacob spent seven years at Merrill Lynch where he was the head of the Distressed Trading group, and also ran the Southeast Asia Distressed Trading business from Merrill Lynch's offices in Hong Kong. He received a BS in Finance and Accounting and an MS in Finance from the University of Wisconsin.

Experience

Archview Investment Group LP Founding Principal 2009 - Present (11 years)

Citigroup, Inc Managing Director 1999 - 2008 (9 years)

Merrill Lynch Managing Director 1992 - 1999 (7 years)

Education

University of Wisconsin-Madison
Master of Science (MS), Finance · (1991 - 1992)

University of Wisconsin-Madison
Bachelor of Business Administration (BBA), Accounting and
Finance · (1986 - 1990)